Teng Fei: Hi, Peter! It's Ella and Emma's birthday soon. How about a surprise party for them?
Peter: Good idea! Let's go and buy something for the party this weekend.
Woman: Good morning. Can I help you?
Teng Fei: Yes, please. How much is this birthday cake?
Woman: We have a sale today. It's 85 yuan, and it comes with some candles.
Peter: Good, we'll take it. How much are those oranges?
Woman: Six yuan a kilo. How many kilos do you want?
Peter: Five kilos, please. Teng Fei, how about some yogurt?
Teng Fei: Sure. How much is the yogurt?
Woman: Five yuan a bottle.
Teng Fei: 10 bottles, please. What's the total?
Woman: 165 yuan.
Teng Fei: Here you are.
Woman: Thank you! Have a nice day
Teng Fei & Peter: Thanks. You too.Listening Scripts